Kirill Lunev

Full Stack Developer

Nof haGalil | 053-438-4484 | kir6498@gmail.com GitHub | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python and JavaScript-based programming with a background in ERP development for more than 10+ years. Conducting projects for the implementation and maintenance of corporate information systems. I also have competencies in the field of formalization and writing of technical tasks, and formalization of customer requirements into functional requirements for the system.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, OOP, SQL, Flask, Javascript, CSS

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Task Management System - Github | Link

Task Management System across Projects and Statuses

- Task management across system users with tracking task completion time
- Adding notes and attaching files to tasks/projects
- Task reports with user-specific access restrictions. Access control for projects based on user roles

Automation of a logistics company

Automation system of interaction between dispatchers and drivers using Telegram

Developed a system of accounting transportation orders in the logistics company, the system allows the company's dispatcher to interact with the drivers through the Telegram bot. Drivers receive, coordinate, stop at route points, and receive final documents via Telegram bot.

EXPERIENCE

ERP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Moscow, Russia

Self-employed

06/2013 - Present

- Implementation of accounting and management automation projects in various companies. 50+ different projects
- Various integration projects using multiple technologies and formats (JSON, API, HTTP sockets, XML, webhooks)

SENIOR ERP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Vladivostok, Russia

DNS | One of the largest electronic companies in Russia. More than 1,000 stores

10/2012 - 05/2013

- Development of a program for the automation of computer assembly accounting at the company's factory
- Setting and monitoring the execution of tasks by other programmers (2 subordinates)

ERP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Vladivostok, Russia

Prodis | Large distribution company, 500+ employees

04/2011 - 09/2012

- Made the transition from the old accounting system to the new one
- Database Administration, developing new features for accounting tasks

JUNIOR ERP SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Vladivostok, Russia

09/2010 - 04/2011

- Iterra | Software implementation and Maintenance company Developed a sales manager's desktop for a trading company
 - Revision of standard 1C configurations, updating configurations, writing reports/treatments, correcting errors, advising users

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Ramat Gan, Israel 12/2022 - 05/2023

Bachelor's degree in Applied Computer Science

VLADIVOSTOK STATE UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS AND SERVICE

Vladivostok, Russia

07/2011

LANGUAGES

Russian- native speaker, English - fluent